Finding Aid for the Andrew West Photographs of the Guelaguetza, 1982-1985
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Color Slides
  - Guelaguetza
    - Ylalag - Sierra, 1982., 20 slides. (Box 1, Folder 16)
      - Ylalag, dancers, 1982
      - Ylalag, couples dancing, 1982
      - Ylalag, couples dancing, 1982
      - Ylalag, couples dancing, 1982
      - Ylalag, couples dancing, 1982
      - Ylalag, couples dancing, 1982
      - Ylalag, couples dancing, 1982
      - Ylalag, couples dancing, 1982
      - Ylalag, couples dancing, 1982
      - Ylalag, couples dancing, 1982
      - Ylalag, couples dancing, 1982
      - Ylalag, couples dancing, 1982
      - Ylalag, couples dancing, 1982
      - Ylalag, couples dancing, 1982
      - Ylalag, couples dancing, 1982
      - Ylalag, couples dancing, 1982
      - Ylalag, couples dancing, 1982
      - Ylalag, couples dancing, 1982
      - Ylalag, couples dancing, 1982
      - Ylalag, couples dancing, 1982
      - Ylalag, couples dancing, 1982
      - Ylalag, couples dancing, 1982
    - Ylalag - Sierra, 1985., 20 slides. (Box 1, Folder 17)
      - Ylalag, back view of woman dancer, 1985
      - Ylalag, performers throwing gifts to spectators, 1985
      - Ylalag, performers throwing gifts to spectators, 1985
      - Ylalag, couples dancing, 1985
      - Ylalag, couples dancing, 1985
      - Ylalag, couples dancing, 1985
      - Ylalag, performers throwing gifts to spectators, 1985
      - Ylalag, couples dancing, 1985
      - Ylalag, couples dancing, 1985
      - Ylalag, couples dancing, 1985
    - Macuiltianguis de la Sierra, 1985., 27 slides. (Box 1, Folder 18)
      - Macuiltianguis, dancer falling off stage, 1985
      - Macuiltianguis, dancer falling off stage, 1985
      - Macuiltianguis, dancers, 1985
      - Macuiltianguis, dancers, 1985
      - Macuiltianguis, dancers, 1985
      - Macuiltianguis, dancers, 1985
      - Macuiltianguis, dancers, 1985
      - Macuiltianguis, dancers, 1985
      - Macuiltianguis, dancers, 1985
      - Macuiltianguis, dancers, 1985
      - Macuiltianguis, dancers, 1985
      - Macuiltianguis, dancers, 1985
      - Macuiltianguis, dancers, 1985
      - Macuiltianguis, dancers, 1985
      - Macuiltianguis, dancers, 1985
      - Macuiltianguis, dancers, 1985
      - Macuiltianguis, dancers, 1985
      - Macuiltianguis, dancers, 1985
      - Macuiltianguis, performers throwing gifts to spectators, 1985
      - Macuiltianguis, performers throwing gifts to spectators, 1985
      - Macuiltianguis, performers throwing gifts to spectators, 1985
      - Macuiltianguis, performers throwing gifts to spectators, 1985
      - Macuiltianguis, performers throwing gifts to spectators, 1985
      - Macuiltianguis, performers throwing gifts to spectators, 1985
      - Macuiltianguis, performers throwing straw hats to spectators, 1985
      - Macuiltianguis, performers throwing straw hats to spectators, 1985
      - Macuiltianguis, women dancing with skirts, 1985
    - San Sebastien Penoles Mixtec or Santa Catarina Estetla, 1985., 32 slides. (Box 1, Folder 19)
      - Santa Catarina Estetla, dancers holding leaves, 1985
      - Santa Catarina Estetla, dancers holding leaves, 1985
      - Santa Catarina Estetla, dancers holding leaves, 1985
      - Santa Catarina Estetla, dancers holding leaves, 1985
      - Santa Catarina Estetla, girl in costume, 1985
      - Santa Catarina Estetla, boy and girl in costume, 1985
      - Santa Catarina Estetla, dancers holding leaves, 1985
      - Santa Catarina Estetla, dancers holding leaves, 1985
      - Santa Catarina Estetla, boy and girl in costume, 1985
      - Santa Catarina Estetla, singers, 1985
      - Santa Catarina Estetla, dancers holding leaves, 1985
      - Santa Catarina Estetla, dancers holding leaves, 1985
      - Santa Catarina Estetla, dancers holding leaves, 1985
      - Santa Catarina Estetla, dancers holding leaves, 1985
      - Santa Catarina Estetla, dancers holding leaves, 1985
      - Santa Catarina Estetla, dancers holding leaves, 1985
      - Santa Catarina Estetla, dancers holding leaves, 1985
      - Santa Catarina Estetla, dancers holding leaves, 1985
      - Santa Catarina Estetla, dancers holding leaves, 1985
      - Santa Catarina Estetla, dancers holding leaves, 1985
      - Santa Catarina Estetla, girl in costume, 1985
      - Santa Catarina Estetla, dancers holding leaves, 1985
      - Santa Catarina Estetla, dancers holding leaves, 1985
      - Santa Catarina Estetla, dancers holding leaves, 1985
      - Santa Catarina Estetla, dancers holding leaves, 1985
      - Santa Catarina Estetla, dancers holding leaves, 1985
      - Santa Catarina Estetla, dancers holding leaves, 1985
      - Santa Catarina Estetla, dancers holding leaves, 1985
      - Santa Catarina Estetla, dancers holding leaves, 1985
      - Santa Catarina Estetla, dancers holding leaves, 1985
      - Santa Catarina Estetla, dancers holding leaves, 1985
      - Santa Catarina Estetla, dancers holding leaves, 1985
    - San Pedro Cajones - Region de la Sierra, 1985., 20 slides. (Box 1, Folder 20)
      - San Pedro Cajonos, dancers, 1985
      - San Pedro Cajonos, dancers, 1985
      - San Pedro Cajonos, dancers, 1985
      - San Pedro Cajonos, dancers, 1985
      - San Pedro Cajonos, dancers, 1985
      - San Pedro Cajonos, dancers, 1985
      - San Pedro Cajonos, dancers, 1985
      - San Pedro Cajonos, dancers, 1985
      - San Pedro Cajonos, dancers, 1985
      - San Pedro Cajonos, dancers, 1985
      - San Pedro Cajonos, dancers, 1985
      - San Pedro Cajonos, dancers, 1985
      - San Pedro Cajonos, dancers, 1985
      - San Pedro Cajonos, dancers holding textile strips, 1985
      - San Pedro Cajonos, dancers holding textile strips, 1985
      - San Pedro Cajonos, dancers, 1985
      - San Pedro Cajonos, dancers, 1985
      - San Pedro Cajonos, dancers holding textile strips, 1985
      - San Pedro Cajonos, dancers holding textile strips, 1985
      - San Pedro Cajonos, dancers, 1985
      - San Pedro Cajonos, dancers, 1985
    - Tuxtepec - Papaloapan, 1985., 39 slides. (Box 1, Folder 21)
      - Tuxtepec, women holding pineapples, 1985
      - Tuxtepec, women holding pineapples, 1985
      - Tuxtepec, women dancers holding pineapples, 1985
      - Tuxtepec, women dancers holding pineapples, 1985
      - Tuxtepec, women dancers holding pineapples, 1985
      - Tuxtepec, women dancers holding pineapples, 1985
      - Tuxtepec, women dancers holding pineapples, 1985
      - Tuxtepec, women dancers holding pineapples, 1985
      - Tuxtepec, women holding pineapples, 1985
      - Tuxtepec, women dancers holding pineapples, 1985
      - Tuxtepec, women dancers holding pineapples, 1985
      - Tuxtepec, women dancers holding pineapples, 1985
      - Tuxtepec, women holding pineapples, 1985
      - Tuxtepec, women and pineapples, 1985
      - Tuxtepec, women holding pineapples, 1985
      - Tuxtepec, women holding pineapples, 1985
      - Tuxtepec, women sitting with pineapples, 1985
      - Tuxtepec, women dancers holding pineapples, 1985
      - Tuxtepec, performers throwing gifts to spectators, 1985
      - Tuxtepec, women holding pineapples, 1985
      - Tuxtepec, women holding pineapples, 1985
      - Tuxtepec, women holding pineapples, 1985
      - Tuxtepec, women holding pineapples, 1985
      - Tuxtepec, women dancers and pineapples, 1985
      - Tuxtepec, women dancers and pineapples, 1985
      - Tuxtepec, women holding pineapples, 1985
      - Tuxtepec, women holding pineapples, 1985
      - Tuxtepec, women holding pineapples, 1985
      - Tuxtepec, women holding pineapples, 1985
      - Tuxtepec, women holding pineapples, 1985
      - Tuxtepec, women dancers and pineapples, 1985
      - Tuxtepec, women dancers and pineapples, 1985
      - Tuxtepec, women dancers and pineapples, 1985
      - Tuxtepec, women dancers and pineapples, 1985
      - Tuxtepec, women holding pineapples, 1985
      - Tuxtepec, women holding pineapples, 1985
      - Tuxtepec, women holding pineapples, 1985
      - Tuxtepec, women dancers holding pineapples, 1985
      - Tuxtepec, women dancers holding pineapples, 1985
    - Flor de Pina - Tuxtepec - Papaloapan, 1982., 11 slides. (Box 1, Folder 22)
      - Flor de Pina, performers throwing gifts to spectators, 1982
      - Flor de Pina, performers throwing gifts to spectators, 1982
      - Flor de Pina, performers throwing gifts to spectators, 1982
      - Flor de Pina, performers throwing gifts to spectators, 1982
      - Flor de Pina, women dancers holding pineapples, 1982
      - Flor de Pina, women dancers holding pineapples, 1982
      - Flor de Pina, women dancers holding pineapples, 1982
      - Flor de Pina, women dancers holding pineapples, 1982
      - Flor de Pina, women dancers holding pineapples, 1982
      - Flor de Pina, women dancers sitting with pineapples, 1982
      - Flor de Pina, women dancers sitting with pineapples, 1982
    - Teotitlán del Valle, 1985., 37 slides. (Box 1, Folder 23)
      - Teotitlán, men dancing wearing large headdresses, 1985
      - Teotitlán, men dancing wearing large headdresses, 1985
      - Teotitlán, men dancing wearing large headdresses, 1985
      - Teotitlán, men dancing wearing large headdresses, 1985
      - Teotitlán, men dancing wearing large headdresses, 1985
      - Teotitlán, men dancing wearing large headdresses, 1985
      - Teotitlán, men dancing wearing large headdresses, 1985
      - Teotitlán, men dancing wearing large headdresses, 1985
      - Teotitlán, men dancing wearing large headdresses, 1985
      - Teotitlán, men dancing wearing large headdresses, 1985
      - Teotitlán, men dancing wearing large headdresses, 1985
      - Teotitlán, men dancing wearing large headdresses, 1985
      - Teotitlán, men dancing wearing large headdresses, 1985
      - Teotitlán, men dancing wearing large headdresses, 1985
      - Teotitlán, men dancing wearing large headdresses, 1985
      - Teotitlán, men dancing wearing large headdresses, 1985
      - Teotitlán, men dancing wearing large headdresses, 1985
      - Teotitlán, men dancing wearing large headdresses, 1985
      - Teotitlán, men dancing wearing large headdresses, 1985
      - Teotitlán, men dancing wearing large headdresses, 1985
      - Teotitlán, men dancing wearing large headdresses, 1985
      - Teotitlán, men dancing wearing large headdresses, 1985
      - Teotitlán, men dancing wearing large headdresses, 1985
      - Teotitlán, men dancing wearing large headdresses, 1985
      - Teotitlán, men dancing wearing large headdresses, 1985
      - Teotitlán, men dancing wearing large headdresses, 1985
      - Teotitlán, men dancing wearing large headdresses, 1985
      - Teotitlán, men dancing wearing large headdresses, 1985
      - Teotitlán, men dancing wearing large headdresses, 1985
      - Teotitlán, men dancing wearing large headdresses, 1985
      - Teotitlán, men dancing wearing large headdresses, 1985
      - Teotitlán, men dancing wearing large headdresses, 1985
      - Teotitlán, men dancing wearing large headdresses, 1985
      - Teotitlán, men dancing wearing large headdresses, 1985
      - Teotitlán, men dancing wearing large headdresses, 1985
      - Teotitlán, men dancing wearing large headdresses, 1985
      - Teotitlán, men dancing wearing large headdresses, 1985
    - Awarding of prizes[?], 1985., 7 slides. (Box 1, Folder 24)
      - Awarding of prizes[?], man and woman standing, 1985
      - Awarding of prizes[?], procession, 1985
      - Awarding of prizes[?], woman dancing, 1985
      - Awarding of prizes[?], woman displaying her skirt, 1985
      - Awarding of prizes[?], woman holding netted bag, 1985
      - Awarding of prizes[?], woman singing, 1985
      - Awarding of prizes[?], woman wearing sash and gold necklace, 1985
  - Saints Day Celebration
    - Saints Day Celebration - Teotitlan de Valle, 1982., 55 slides. (Box 1, Folder 26)
      - Saints Day, back of large headdress, 1982
      - Saints Day, band members walking, 1982
      - Saints Day, band members, 1982
      - Saints Day, band members, 1982
      - Saints Day, boys wearing soldier costumes, 1982
      - Saints Day, dancing feet, 1982
      - Saints Day, drums [band], 1982
      - Saints Day, face of boy in soldier costume, 1982
      - Saints Day, face of man in soldier costume, 1982
      - Saints Day, face of man wearing large headdress, 1982
      - Saints Day, faces of boys wearing soldier costumes, 1982
      - Saints Day, feathered headdresses surrounding a man reading, 1982
      - Saints Day, girl wearing white gloves, 1982
      - Saints Day, girls dancing, 1982
      - Saints Day, groups of band members and men in large headdresses, 1982
      - Saints Day, groups of band members and men in large headdresses, 1982
      - Saints Day, legs of men running, 1982
      - Saints Day, man holding large headdress, 1982
      - Saints Day, man holding sword, 1982
      - Saints Day, man in costume drinking a beer, 1982
      - Saints Day, man looking at a polaroid picture, 1982
      - Saints Day, man marching in soldier costume, 1982
      - Saints Day, man surrounded by headdresses, 1982
      - Saints Day, man surrounded by headdresses, 1982
      - Saints Day, man wearing black mask and children in costume, 1982
      - Saints Day, man wearing black mask and children in costume, 1982
      - Saints Day, man wearing black mask and children in costume, 1982
      - Saints Day, man wearing large headdress, 1982
      - Saints Day, man wearing large headdress, 1982
      - Saints Day, man wearing large headdress, 1982
      - Saints Day, man wearing large headdress, 1982
      - Saints Day, man wearing large headdress, 1982
      - Saints Day, man wearing large headdress, 1982
      - Saints Day, man wielding a sword, 1982
      - Saints Day, man wielding sword, 1982
      - Saints Day, man wielding sword, 1982
      - Saints Day, man wielding sword, 1982
      - Saints Day, man wielding sword, 1982
      - Saints Day, men and headdresses, 1982
      - Saints Day, men in large headdresses walking and band playing, 1982
      - Saints Day, men wearing black masks, 1982
      - Saints Day, men wearing black masks, 1982
      - Saints Day, men wearing large headdresses viewing Polariod photograph, 1982
      - Saints Day, men wearing large headdresses, 1982
      - Saints Day, men wearing large headdresses, 1982
      - Saints Day, men wearing large headdresses, 1982
      - Saints Day, men wearing large headdresses, 1982
      - Saints Day, men wearing large headdresses, 1982
      - Saints Day, men wearing large headdresses, 1982
      - Saints Day, men wearing large headdresses, 1982
      - Saints Day, men wearing large headdresses, 1982
      - Saints Day, men wearing large headdresses, 1982
      - Saints Day, men wearing large headdresses, 1982
      - Saints Day, various performers in costume, 1982
      - Saints Day, various performers in costume, 1982
  - Ocotlan
    - Ocotlan, 1982., 17 slides. (Box 1, Folder 27)
      - Ocotlan, clay figurines, 1982
      - Ocotlan, clay figurines, 1982
      - Ocotlan, kneading clay with feet, 1982
      - Ocotlan, kneading clay with feet, 1982
      - Ocotlan, modeling (sculpture) clay figurines, 1982
      - Ocotlan, modeling (sculpture) clay figurines, 1982
      - Ocotlan, modeling (sculpture) clay figurines, 1982
      - Ocotlan, modeling (sculpture) clay figurines, 1982
      - Ocotlan, modeling (sculpture) clay figurines, 1982
      - Ocotlan, modeling (sculpture) clay into blocks, 1982
      - Ocotlan, modeling (sculpture) clay, 1982
      - Ocotlan, modeling (sculpture) clay, 1982
      - Ocotlan, modeling (sculpture) clay, 1982
      - Ocotlan, painting clay figurines, 1982
      - Ocotlan, painting clay figurines, 1982
      - Ocotlan, painting clay figurines, 1982
      - Ocotlan, painting clay figurines, 1982
  - Oaxaca
    - Oaxaca, 1982 & 1985., 110 slides. (Box 1, Folder 28)
      - Oaxaca, Basilica of Nuestra Señora de la Soledad (Our Lady of Solitude), 1982 or 1985
      - Oaxaca, Basilica of Nuestra Señora de la Soledad (Our Lady of Solitude), 1982 or 1985
      - Oaxaca, Coca-Cola truck and bottles, 1982 or 1985
      - Oaxaca, Monte Albán (archaeological site), 1982 or 1985
      - Oaxaca, Monte Albán (archaeological site), 1982 or 1985
      - Oaxaca, Monte Albán (archaeological site), 1982 or 1985
      - Oaxaca, Monte Albán (archaeological site), 1982 or 1985
      - Oaxaca, Monte Albán (archaeological site), 1982 or 1985
      - Oaxaca, Monte Albán (archaeological site), 1982 or 1985
      - Oaxaca, Monte Albán (archaeological site), 1982 or 1985
      - Oaxaca, Monte Albán (archaeological site), 1982 or 1985
      - Oaxaca, Monte Albán (archaeological site), 1982 or 1985
      - Oaxaca, Monte Albán (archaeological site), 1982 or 1985
      - Oaxaca, Monte Albán (archaeological site), 1982 or 1985
      - Oaxaca, Monte Albán (archaeological site), 1982 or 1985
      - Oaxaca, Monte Albán (archaeological site), 1982 or 1985
      - Oaxaca, Monte Albán (archaeological site), 1982 or 1985
      - Oaxaca, Monte Albán (archaeological site), 1982 or 1985
      - Oaxaca, Monte Albán (archaeological site), 1982 or 1985
      - Oaxaca, Monte Albán (archaeological site), 1982 or 1985
      - Oaxaca, Monte Albán (archaeological site), 1982 or 1985
      - Oaxaca, Monte Albán (archaeological site), 1982 or 1985
      - Oaxaca, Santo Domingo cathedral and museum, 1982 or 1985
      - Oaxaca, Santo Domingo cathedral and museum, 1982 or 1985
      - Oaxaca, Santo Domingo cathedral and museum, 1982 or 1985
      - Oaxaca, aerial view of crops, 1982 or 1985
      - Oaxaca, aerial view, 1982 or 1985
      - Oaxaca, aerial view, 1982 or 1985
      - Oaxaca, aerial view, 1982 or 1985
      - Oaxaca, aerial view, 1982 or 1985
      - Oaxaca, aerial view, 1982 or 1985
      - Oaxaca, balloon vendor, 1982 or 1985
      - Oaxaca, balloon vendor, 1982 or 1985
      - Oaxaca, balloon vendor, 1982 or 1985
      - Oaxaca, boy and Coca-Cola sign, 1982 or 1985
      - Oaxaca, boy and student desks, 1982 or 1985
      - Oaxaca, boy blowing-up balloon, 1982 or 1985
      - Oaxaca, boy in cropfields, 1982 or 1985
      - Oaxaca, boy in cropfields, 1982 or 1985
      - Oaxaca, boy playing in sand, 1982 or 1985
      - Oaxaca, boy wearing cowboy hat, 1982 or 1985
      - Oaxaca, boy with woven baskets and mats, 1982 or 1985
      - Oaxaca, boy, 1982 or 1985
      - Oaxaca, boys and dog, 1982 or 1985
      - Oaxaca, boys and dog, 1982 or 1985
      - Oaxaca, butcher and pig head, 1982 or 1985
      - Oaxaca, cathedral, 1982 or 1985
      - Oaxaca, children dressed in ceremonial attire, 1982 or 1985
      - Oaxaca, children dressed in ceremonial attire, 1982 or 1985
      - Oaxaca, children holding hands, 1982 or 1985
      - Oaxaca, construction workers, 1982 or 1985
      - Oaxaca, construction workers, 1982 or 1985
      - Oaxaca, cropfields, 1982 or 1985
      - Oaxaca, cropfields, 1982 or 1985
      - Oaxaca, croplands, 1982 or 1985
      - Oaxaca, distance view of boys and farm animals, 1982 or 1985
      - Oaxaca, doorway into clothing store, 1982 or 1985
      - Oaxaca, face of boy, 1982 or 1985
      - Oaxaca, farm animals crossing dirt road, 1982 or 1985
      - Oaxaca, farm animals, 1982 or 1985
      - Oaxaca, farming the cropfields, 1982 or 1985
      - Oaxaca, farming the cropfields, 1982 or 1985
      - Oaxaca, garden, 1982 or 1985
      - Oaxaca, girl and clothing store, 1982 or 1985
      - Oaxaca, girl, 1982 or 1985
      - Oaxaca, girls, 1982 or 1985
      - Oaxaca, goats in field, 1982 or 1985
      - Oaxaca, goats in field, 1982 or 1985
      - Oaxaca, goats, 1982 or 1985
      - Oaxaca, goats, 1982 or 1985
      - Oaxaca, horse holding baskets, 1982 or 1985
      - Oaxaca, horse pulling cart of children, 1982 or 1985
      - Oaxaca, landscape, 1982 or 1985
      - Oaxaca, landscape, 1982 or 1985
      - Oaxaca, landscape, 1982 or 1985
      - Oaxaca, landscape, 1982 or 1985
      - Oaxaca, landscape, 1982 or 1985
      - Oaxaca, man and boy riding mule, 1982 or 1985
      - Oaxaca, man and ropes, 1982 or 1985
      - Oaxaca, man fixing television, 1982 or 1985
      - Oaxaca, man holding old trumpet, 1982 or 1985
      - Oaxaca, man in cowboy hat, 1982 or 1985
      - Oaxaca, man riding tractor in cropfields, 1982 or 1985
      - Oaxaca, man riding tractor in cropfields, 1982 or 1985
      - Oaxaca, man riding tractor in cropfields, 1982 or 1985
      - Oaxaca, man sitting on bench, 1982 or 1985
      - Oaxaca, man walking cattle down dirt road, 1982 or 1985
      - Oaxaca, mules and cornfield, 1982 or 1985
      - Oaxaca, old man in cowboy hat, 1982 or 1985
      - Oaxaca, old man in cowboy hat, 1982 or 1985
      - Oaxaca, old man reading a book outside, 1982 or 1985
      - Oaxaca, old man walking down sidewalk, 1982 or 1985
      - Oaxaca, old woman, 1982 or 1985
      - Oaxaca, pair of cattle on yoke, 1982 or 1985
      - Oaxaca, pair of cattle on yoke, 1982 or 1985
      - Oaxaca, pair of cattle on yoke, 1982 or 1985
      - Oaxaca, people waiting by building, 1982 or 1985
      - Oaxaca, people waiting by building, 1982 or 1985
      - Oaxaca, pigs, 1982 or 1985
      - Oaxaca, pigs, 1982 or 1985
      - Oaxaca, policewomen, 1982 or 1985
      - Oaxaca, potted plants outside restaurant, 1982 or 1985
      - Oaxaca, vines climbing building archways, 1982 or 1985
      - Oaxaca, white building, 1982 or 1985
      - Oaxaca, woman breastfeeding toddler in crowd of men, 1982 or 1985
      - Oaxaca, woman walking by barred window, 1982 or 1985
      - Oaxaca, woman walking with basket on head, 1982 or 1985
      - Oaxaca, women and bicycles, 1982 or 1985
      - Oaxaca, women walking down rural road, 1982 or 1985
      - Oaxaca, women walking up dirt path, 1982 or 1985
  - [Guelaguetza?]
    - Spectators, Performers, Close-ups, 1982 & 1985., 99 slides. (Box 1, Folder 29)
      - Guelaguetza[?], back view of woman dancer, 1982 or 1985
      - Guelaguetza[?], dancers close-up, 1982 or 1985
      - Guelaguetza[?], dancers close-up, 1982 or 1985
      - Guelaguetza[?], dancers close-up, 1982 or 1985
      - Guelaguetza[?], dancers close-up, 1982 or 1985
      - Guelaguetza[?], dancers close-up, 1982 or 1985
      - Guelaguetza[?], dancers close-up, 1982 or 1985
      - Guelaguetza[?], dancers close-up, 1982 or 1985
      - Guelaguetza[?], dancers wrapped in blanket [view from behind], 1982 or 1985
      - Guelaguetza[?], dancers, 1982 or 1985
      - Guelaguetza[?], earring close-up, 1982 or 1985
      - Guelaguetza[?], earring close-up, 1982 or 1985
      - Guelaguetza[?], earring close-up, 1982 or 1985
      - Guelaguetza[?], earring close-up, 1982 or 1985
      - Guelaguetza[?], earring close-up, 1982 or 1985
      - Guelaguetza[?], girl dancer close-up, 1982 or 1985
      - Guelaguetza[?], girl dancer close-up, 1982 or 1985
      - Guelaguetza[?], girl dancer close-up, 1982 or 1985
      - Guelaguetza[?], gourd tied around waist, 1982 or 1985
      - Guelaguetza[?], hand close-up, 1982 or 1985
      - Guelaguetza[?], hands holding flowers close-up, 1982 or 1985
      - Guelaguetza[?], leather sandals, 1982 or 1985
      - Guelaguetza[?], leather sandals, 1982 or 1985
      - Guelaguetza[?], man close-up, 1982 or 1985
      - Guelaguetza[?], man close-up, 1982 or 1985
      - Guelaguetza[?], man close-up, 1982 or 1985
      - Guelaguetza[?], man close-up, 1982 or 1985
      - Guelaguetza[?], man close-up, 1982 or 1985
      - Guelaguetza[?], man close-up, 1982 or 1985
      - Guelaguetza[?], man close-up, 1982 or 1985
      - Guelaguetza[?], man holding gourd, 1982 or 1985
      - Guelaguetza[?], man holding gourd, 1982 or 1985
      - Guelaguetza[?], man holding gourd, 1982 or 1985
      - Guelaguetza[?], man holding gourd, 1982 or 1985
      - Guelaguetza[?], man holding gourd, 1982 or 1985
      - Guelaguetza[?], man holding gourd, 1982 or 1985